Contact

jes04408@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jessica-saint-b98a19114 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Registered Nurses

IV

Healthcare

Languages

English

Certifications ACLS

Jessica Saint

EMR Consultant and Travel RN

Helena, Alabama

Summary

Travel Nurse and EMR Consultant. Total of 9 years RN experience, 4 years as a travel RN. I have been a consultant for numerous EMR conversions I have worked with the following computer systems: Epic, Meditech, Cerner, and Sorian. Energetic, hard-working, and punctual. Always looking for new opportunities.

Experience

Medasource
CERNER ATE Consultant
February 2017 - Present (3 years 6 months)

Advantage RN

Travel RN

May 2014 - Present (6 years 3 months)

Adapting quickly to change in new facilities every 3 months. Caring for high acuity patients from multiple ailments. Managing complex IV drips. Communicating effectively with patients, their families, and other healthcare professionals. Pulling sheaths post cardiac cath. Managing chest tubes, central lines, drains, etc. Dependable, team player, hard-working.

Divurgent
EPIC ATE Consultant
October 2016 - November 2016 (2 months)

UAB Hospital

RN

February 2012 - April 2014 (2 years 3 months)

My responsibilities included managing IV drips, caring for high acuity stroke patients post TPA infusion. Monitoring vital signs post cardiac cath. Caring for post surgical patients with multiple tubes and drains. Providing adequate pain management. Communicating effectively with patients, their families, and other healthcare professionals.

Education

University of Alabama at Birmingham

Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2009 - 2011)